Hi everyone, I thought I would take three minutes
to let you know
where I'm going to be speaking publicly in Canada
the United States and Europe
now and until the end of 2018.
I've been touring for about three months
discussing the issues of meaning and responsibility
raised in my books, 12 rules for life, and maps of meaning.
My wife Tammy and I have already been in 60 cities
and I've spoken to about 200,000 people.
Here are the Canadian, American, and European cities
I will be traveling to over the next five months
Calgary, Friday, July 27th.
Edmonton, Saturday, July 28th.
Winnipeg, Sunday, July 29th.
Regina, Tuesday, August 14th.
Saskatoon, Wednesday, August 15th.
Rochester, Wednesday, September 5th.
Westbury, Thursday, September 6th.
Wallingford, Friday, September 7th.
Baltimore, Sunday, September 9th.
Durham, Monday, September 10th.
Miami, Thursday, September 13th.
Orlando, Friday, September 14th.
St.Petersburg, Saturday, September 15th.
Jacksonville, Sunday, September 16th.
Cincinnati, Tuesday, September 18th.
Cleveland, Wednesday September 19th.
Grand Rapids, Thursday, September 20th.
Des Moines, Tuesday, October 2nd
St. Louis, Wednesday, October 3rd.
Kansas City, Thursday, October 4th.
Denver, Sunday, October 7th.
Colorado Springs, Monday, October 8th.
San Antonio, Wednesday, October 10th.
Irving, Thursday, October 11th.
Honolulu, Wednesday, November 21st.
Los Angeles, Saturday, December 1st.
Back in Canada. Calgary, Thursday, December 4th.
Vancouver, Wednesday, December 5th.
Then, it's off to Europe.
Dublin, Sunday, October 21st.
Oslo, Tuesday, October 23rd.
Manchester, Thursday, October 25th.
Oxford, Friday, October 26th.
Glasgow, Saturday, October 27th.
Edinburgh, Sunday, October 28th.
Amsterdam, Tuesday, October 30th.
Cambridge, Thursday, November 1st.
Helsinki, Sunday, November 4th.
Stockholm, Monday, November 5th.
And Birmingham, Wednesday, November 7th.
We will be adding some more cities
to the European leg of this tour,
they will be announced soon.
And also, we are going to Australia
in February, and then back to Europe in April of 2019.
Those dates will be announced in the relatively near future.
It's been really something to tour around like this
and these events have been extremely positive.
So if you are inclined to come out and hear me lecture
you'd be more than welcome.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.